bikeexif.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy policy | Bike EXIF

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used to improve our website or to send periodic emails. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes. (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser—if you allow—that enables the site to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction, so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Comments**  
We use Disqus for our commenting system. You can find Disqus’ privacy policy [here](http://docs.disqus.com/help/30/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at PO Box 668, Warkworth 0941, New Zealand, or via email to editor@bikeexif.com.
